This application allows quick analysis of financial market
data, fx's, cryptos, US listed ETS and stocks
in one dashboard.
I can select multiple instruments and request historical
price data in a single step.
The app automatically fetches and validates the data.
Here I can see historical prices, charts, and
correlation between all selected instruments.
This view helps to identify relationships between assets,
for example how stocks behave relative to each
other and other benchmarks.
Here in benchmark metrics, stocks like Microsoft and
Nike are compared against benchmarks such as SPY,
QQQ, and GLD using beta, volatility, and other
metrics.
Each metric includes a short explanation making the
dashboard useful also for learning and decision support.
The project is built with Python and Streamlit
and designed as a base for future AI
-driven insights.